Guide to the Amsterdam News photograph archive, Series A. Subject Files P-T, 1920-2012.
Amsterdam News photograph archive
- Series A. Subject Files A
  - Subject Files T
    - Teena Marie (Box A-115, Folder 223)
    - Teenagers (Box A-115, Folder 224)
    - The Teenagers (See also Lyman, Louis) (Box A-115, Folder 225)
      Photographer if identified: M. Jaffe
    - Teer, Barbara Ann (Box A-115, Folder 226)
      Photographer if identified: Norman Frederick, Adeyemi Lythcott, Whitestone Photo, Bert Andrews, Steven Block Associates, Bill Whiting Assoc., Bilal Farid, Harris Photo, Bill Moore, Bruce Williams,
    - Teer, Barbara Ann (Box A-115, Folder 227)
      Photographer if identified: BelFon, Pictorial Enterprise
    - Tefferoa, John D. (Box A-115, Folder 228)
      One print has staple through edge. 1 print is of Barbara Ann Teer.
      Photographer if identified: Ace Creative Photo
    - Tegegne, Yetesha-Work (Box A-115, Folder 229)
    - Teich, Julius (Box A-115, Folder 230)
    - Tekle, Afewerk (Box A-115, Folder 231)
    - Teleflora (Box A-115, Folder 232)
    - TelePrompter (Box A-115, Folder 233)
    - Telestard, Darwin (Box A-115, Folder 234)
    - "Tell Pharaoh" (Box A-115, Folder 235)
      Photographer if identified: Billie Billing
    - Teller, Myrtle (Box A-115, Folder 236)
    - Television Series & Shows (Box A-115, Folder 237)
      2 sets of 2 prints are stuck together with paste.
      Photographer if identified: Kenneth Love, Gene Bagnato,
    - Temple, Edw. S. (Box A-115, Folder 238)
    - Temple of Liberation (Box A-115, Folder 239)
    - Washington Temple (Box A-115, Folder 240)
      One print has staple through edge. 1 print has typescript caption stapled to recto.
      Photographer if identified: Michael J. Henry
    - Templeton, Alec (Box A-115, Folder 241)
      Photographer if identified: U.S.A.A.F.
    - Tempo (Lionel Hampton's Dog) (Box A-115, Folder 242)
      2 prints are stuck together with paste. 1 print is of Tempo Band Of The Pipers.
      Photographer if identified: Cecil Layne, Bob Head
    - Tempo Club (Box A-115, Folder 243)
    - The Temprees (Box A-115, Folder 244)
    - Tempro, James N. (Box A-115, Folder 245)
      Photographer if identified: NYFD
    - The Temps (Box A-115, Folder 246)
    - Ten Club (Box A-115, Folder 247)
    - Ten Gents (Box A-115, Folder 248)
    - Ten Men (Box A-115, Folder 249)
    - Tenants Council (Box A-115, Folder 250)
      2 prints stuck to folder. 3 prints have newspaper clipping taped to verso. One print has staple through edge. 1 print has rubylith mask taped to recto.
      Photographer if identified: NYCHA, James Gilbert, Bro. David McAdams, L. St. Clair Dummett, Gilbert Pictorial Enterprise, A. Hansen, International News Photo, Bill Hayes, United Press International
    - Tennyson, Sydney Earl (Box A-115, Folder 251)
      Photographer if identified: Moss Photo Service
    - Tents (Box A-115, Folder 252)
    - Terp, Pop Top (Box A-115, Folder 253)
    - Terrance, Holliday (Box A-115, Folder 254)
    - Alpage Terrell (Box A-115, Folder 255)
    - Terrell, Amy (Box A-115, Folder 256)
      Photographer if identified: Newell Johnson
    - Temptations (Box A-116, Folder 1)
      2 prints have staples through edge. 2 prints stapled together. 1 print has rubylith mask.
      Photographer if identified: James J. Kriegsmann, George E. Joseph, Motown
    - Temptations (Box A-116, Folder 2)
    - Terrell, Carrie Mrs. (Box A-116, Folder 3)
      Photographer if identified: Karl Crutchfield, Harris Photo, A. Hansen,
    - Terrell, Dino (Box A-116, Folder 4)
    - Terrell, Ernie (Box A-116, Folder 5)
      Also one single-leaf press release.
    - Terrell, Frederick J. (Box A-116, Folder 6)
    - Terrell, Leonard E. (Rev.) (Box A-116, Folder 7)
      Photographer if identified: James Gilbert, Weems Photo Studio, A. Hansen, Harris Photo,
    - Terrell, Louie (Box A-116, Folder 8)
    - Terrell, Mary (Box A-116, Folder 9)
      Empty negative envelope, dated 6/22/49.
    - Terrell, Mary Church (Box A-116, Folder 10)
      Also one velox print, 1 envelope of negatives.
    - 1 - Mary Church Terrell & Group Dummett (Box A-116, Folder 10)
      Dated 9/21/49. 1 loose 6"x6" negative. 1 image total.
    - Terrell, Pha (Box A-116, Folder 11)
    - Terrell, Tammi (Box A-116, Folder 12)
    - Terrence, Dr. A. C. (Box A-116, Folder 13)
      2 stereotype matrices, with captions stapled to recto.
    - Terrey, Thomas (Box A-116, Folder 14)
    - Terry, Amy (Box A-116, Folder 15)
    - Terry, Anna (Box A-116, Folder 16)
    - Terry, Beatrice (Box A-116, Folder 17)
    - Terry, Benson (Box A-116, Folder 18)
      Photographer if identified: Zodiac Photographers
    - Terry, Betty (Box A-116, Folder 19)
      1 print has typescript caption stapled to verso.
    - Terry, Bob (Box A-116, Folder 20)
    - Terry, Charles Mr. & Mrs. (Box A-116, Folder 21)
    - Terry, Clark (Box A-116, Folder 22)
      Also one velox print, press release. One print has staple through edge.
    - Terry, Dennis L. (Box A-116, Folder 23)
    - Terry, Doug (Box A-116, Folder 24)
    - Terry, Douglas (Box A-116, Folder 25)
    - Terry, Elbert J. (Box A-116, Folder 26)
      1 loose cardboard matte.
      Photographer if identified: Nichols, L. St. Clair Dummett,
    - Terry, Elbert (Mrs.) See Mr. & Mrs. Felix Douse (Box A-116, Folder 27)
    - Terry, Ellen (Box A-116, Folder 28)
    - Terry, Faye (Box A-116, Folder 29)
    - Terry, Frank W. (Box A-116, Folder 30)
      Also 2 velox prints. 1 print has caption stapled to recto.
    - George Terry (Box A-116, Folder 31)
    - Terry, Elder James (Box A-116, Folder 32)
    - Terry, June (Box A-116, Folder 33)
    - Terry, Lanie Mrs. (Box A-116, Folder 34)
    - Terry, Lee F. (Dr. & Mrs.) (Box A-116, Folder 35)
    - Terry, Lloyd (Box A-116, Folder 36)
      Photographer if identified: Gilbert Pictorial Enterprise, Arnold Hinton
    - Terry, Lloyd (See Dorothy Fleming) (Box A-116, Folder 37)
    - Terry, Odell (Box A-116, Folder 38)
    - Terry, Patricia (Box A-116, Folder 39)
    - Terry, Randolph (Box A-116, Folder 40)
    - Terry, Raymond (Box A-116, Folder 41)
    - Terry, Ronald Rev. (Box A-116, Folder 42)
    - Terry, Ronnie (3 ring charity championship fight) (Box A-116, Folder 43)
    - Rosalie Terry (Box A-116, Folder 44)
    - Terry, Sonny (Box A-116, Folder 45)
      Also one paper stereotype matrix. Most prints are with Brownie McGhee.
    - The Terry Singers (Box A-116, Folder 46)
    - Terry, Thelma (Box A-116, Folder 47)
    - Terry "Tippy" Day (Box A-116, Folder 48)
      One paper stereotype matrix with caption.
    - Terry, Wallace (Box A-116, Folder 49)
    - Tex, Joe (Box A-116, Folder 50)
      1 print has press release stapled to recto. One print has staple through edge.
      Photographer if identified: James J. Kriegsmann, Joe Broussard,
    - Texas Southern Univ. (Box A-116, Folder 51)
    - Thacker, Bernard (Box A-116, Folder 52)
      Photographer if identified: Si Chi Ko
    - Thacker, Tom (Box A-116, Folder 53)
    - Thad Jones - Mel Lewis Orchestra (Box A-116, Folder 54)
    - Christopher Thaddis (Box A-116, Folder 55)
    - Thames, Judy (Box A-116, Folder 56)
    - Thames, Judith (Box A-116, Folder 57)
    - Thamon, Eugene (Box A-116, Folder 58)
    - Thanksgiving (Box A-116, Folder 59)
      Also one velox print, 2 envelopes of negatives. 2 prints are stuck together with paste.
      Photographer if identified: Lensman, L. St. Clair Dummett, Bob Jones, Nichols,
    - 1 - Thanksgiving Day Pic Nichols (Box A-116, Folder 59)
      Dated 11-15-1951. 1 strip and 1 loose frame of 6"x6" negatives. 3 images total.
    - 2 - Thanksgiving shot Weisbecker Market Nichols (Box A-116, Folder 59)
      Dated 11-16-1948. 1 loose 6"x6" negative. 1 image total.
    - Thant, U (Box A-116, Folder 60)
    - Tharpe, Rosetta (Sister) (Box A-116, Folder 61)
      Also 3 stereotype matrices. 1 print torn in half.
      Photographer if identified: James [illeg.], James J. Kriegsmann,
    - Thart, Diane (Box A-116, Folder 62)
    - Thatcher, Margaret Mrs. (Box A-116, Folder 63)
      Line drawing of Thatcher.
    - Thaxton, Hubert Mack (Box A-116, Folder 64)
      Also one velox print. 1 Polaroid print mounted on paper.
    - Thaxton, Joesph Mrs. (Box A-116, Folder 65)
      Photographer if identified: Wide World Photos, Chans Photographers
    - Thaxton, Lydia (Box A-116, Folder 66)
      Photographer if identified: Burley Photo Syndicate, Bro. David McAdams,
    - Thaxton, Mack (See Hubert Mack Thaxton) (Box A-116, Folder 67)
    - Sam Theard (Box A-116, Folder 68)
      Also one paper stereotype matrix. 1 print in envelope.
    - Theater (Box A-116, Folder 69)
      Photographer if identified: Bert Andrews, Larry Brown, Juanita Howard, Friedman-Abeles, Pictorial Enterprise, Unique Blends, Ken Howard, Martha Swope,
    - Theater (Box A-116, Folder 70)
      Also one velox print. 1 print mounted to theater schedule.
      Photographer if identified: Kwame Brathwaite, Ken Howard, Bert Andrews, Frank Gimpana, Anita Feldman Shevett, Troi Lancaster, Eric S. Fordham, Unique Blends, Gerry Goodstein, BelFon, Javier Munoz, Frederk Ohringer, Pictorial Enterprise, Larry Brown,
    - Theater (Box A-116, Folder 71)
      Also 1 newspaper clipping.
      Photographer if identified: Karma Stanley, Bill Moore, Images Plus, Pictorial Enterprise, Andrea Brizzi, Bert Andrews, David LeShay, Martha Swope, Lee Abramson,
    - Theater (Box A-116, Folder 72)
      Also 1 postcard for "A Visit," 1 velox print.
      Photographer if identified: Bert Andrews, James Davis, Pictorial Enterprise, Martha Swope, Bill Hilton,
    - Theater (Box A-116, Folder 73)
      Also one velox print, program from "Roughshod Up The Mountain."
      Photographer if identified: Bruce Williams, Robert F. Holden, Jules Allen, Jerry Kean, Berk A. Costello, Bert Andrews, Carol Rosegg, James Gilbert, Martha Swope,
    - Theater (Box A-116, Folder 74)
      Photographer if identified: Bert Andrews, Austin Trevett, Michael Ortiz, Martha Swope, Gerry Goodstein, Nikki Grimes, Richard Braaten, Kenn Duncan, Carol Rosegg,
    - Theater (Box A-116, Folder 75)
      8 prints have staples through edge.
      Photographer if identified: Robert Holden, Akmal, Bert Andrews, Terrance Carney, Vernon Allamby, Angie Coqueran, Susan Cook,
    - Theater (Box A-116, Folder 76)
      Photographer if identified: Kees De Graaff, Bill Pryor, Ken Howard, Gerry Goodstein, Terrance Carney, Douglas Harris, Martha Swope, Lloyd Yearwood, Bert Andrews, James Gilbert, Bryan D. Hall, Doug Harris, Robert Holden,
    - Theater (Box A-116, Folder 77)
      Photographer if identified: Carol Rosegg, Robert F. Holden, Bill Moore, Lois Greenfield, Terrance Carney, Bert Andrews, Marc P. Anderson, Martha Swope, Sherlock Robinson, Martha Holmes, Friedman-Abeles,
    - Theater (Box A-116, Folder 78)
      Photographer if identified: Jerry Vezzuso, Terrance Carney, Johan Elbers, Jerry Engelbach,
    - Theater (Ain't Misbehaving) (Box A-116, Folder 79)
    - Theater (Beautiful Ones, The) (Box A-116, Folder 80)
    - Theater (Dream Girls) (Box A-116, Folder 81)
    - Theater (Good Sport, A) (Box A-116, Folder 82)
      Photographer if identified: Van Peele
    - Theater (Joe Egg) (Box A-116, Folder 83)
    - Theater (Love Triangle) (Box A-116, Folder 84)
      Photographer if identified: Bruce Williams
    - Theater (Tap Dance Kid) (Box A-116, Folder 85)
    - Theater (Two Can Play) (Box A-116, Folder 86)
    - Theater (Your Arm's Too Short To Box With God) (Box A-116, Folder 87)
    - Theater (We Got To Fight Apartheid) (Box A-116, Folder 88)
    - Harlem Jazz Theater (Box A-116, Folder 89)
    - Thelwell, Beverly F. (Box A-116, Folder 90)
    - Thenstead, Adolph (Mrs.) (Box A-116, Folder 91)
    - Theo The Magician (Box A-116, Folder 92)
    - Theophilas, Abuna (Box A-116, Folder 93)
      Photographer if identified: Thom Loughman,
    - Theresa Hotel (Box A-116, Folder 94)
      Photographer if identified: Sam Hamoy
    - Theresa Hotel (now Theresa Towers) (Box A-116, Folder 95)
      Also newspaper clippings. Copies of letter to Mayor Lindsay. Press packet with list of businesses in Theresa Towers.
    - Mother Loretta Theresa (Box A-116, Folder 96)
    - Theus, Lucius (Box A-116, Folder 97)
      Also 2 velox prints, press release.
    - Thibodeaux, James (Box A-116, Folder 98)
    - Thibodeaux, Jeanne (Box A-116, Folder 99)
    - Thielmans, Toots (Box A-116, Folder 100)
    - Thigpen, Amanda (Box A-116, Folder 101)
      Photographer if identified: James J. Kriegsmann, Bob Head
    - Thigpen, Lynne (Box A-116, Folder 102)
      Photographer if identified: Gerry Goodstein, Roger Greenawalt
    - Third World (Box A-116, Folder 103)
      Also 1 halftone print, 1 velox print.
      Photographer if identified: Charles Reilly, Peterkin Photo, Dominique, Kim Gottlieb
    - Thobjane, Gabriel (Box A-116, Folder 104)
    - Thodes, Hari (Box A-116, Folder 105)
    - Thomas, Adolphus (Box A-116, Folder 106)
    - Thomas, Albert (Box A-116, Folder 107)
    - Thomas, Albertha C. (Box A-116, Folder 108)
    - Thomas, Allen (Box A-116, Folder 109)
    - Thomas, Alvin Mrs. (Box A-116, Folder 110)
    - Thomas, Alvin I. Dr. (Box A-116, Folder 111)
    - Thomas, Art (Box A-116, Folder 112)
      Photographer if identified: Ray A. Moss
    - Thomas, Arthur (Box A-116, Folder 113)
    - Thomas, Arthur (Box A-116, Folder 114)
      Also 2 velox prints, One halftone print. 1 print is of Arthur B. Thomas.
    - Thomas, B. (Box A-116, Folder 115)
      Photographer if identified: Studio Graphics
    - Thomas, Ben (Box A-116, Folder 116)
    - Thomas, Betty (Box A-116, Folder 117)
    - Thomas, Bill (Box A-116, Folder 118)
      2 different Bill Thomases.
    - Thomas, Blanche K. (Box A-116, Folder 119)
      Also memorial pamphlets from 8-23-1977.
    - Thomas, Bob (Box A-116, Folder 120)
      Photographer if identified: Harold Barnett
    - Thomas, Bob (Box A-116, Folder 121)
    - Thomas, Brenda (Box A-116, Folder 122)
      Photographer if identified: Bill Whiting
    - Thomas, C. W. (Box A-116, Folder 123)
      Photographer if identified: Nikki Grimes
    - Thomas, Carl (Box A-116, Folder 124)
    - Thomas, Carla (Box A-116, Folder 125)
    - Thomas, Carol (Box A-116, Folder 126)
    - Thomas, Carol M. (Box A-116, Folder 127)
    - Thomas, Charles (Box A-116, Folder 128)
    - Thomas, Charles A. (Box A-116, Folder 129)
    - Thomas, Charles A. (Box A-116, Folder 130)
    - Thomas, Charles C. (Box A-116, Folder 131)
    - Thomas, Charles Columbus (Box A-116, Folder 132)
    - Thomas, Charles E. Rev. (Box A-116, Folder 133)
      Photographer if identified: New Jersey Newsphotos
    - Thomas, Charles H. Jr. (Box A-116, Folder 134)
    - Thomas, Charles H. Jr. Dr. (Box A-116, Folder 135)
      Photographer if identified: Post Office Department Photo
    - Thomas, Charlotte (Box A-116, Folder 136)
    - Thomas, Chesterfield (Box A-116, Folder 137)
    - Thomas, Conrada D. (Mrs.) (Box A-116, Folder 138)
    - Thomas, Constance (Box A-116, Folder 139)
    - Thomas, David M. (Box A-116, Folder 140)
    - Thomas, Delores (Box A-116, Folder 141)
    - Thomas, Deloris Mrs. (Box A-116, Folder 142)
    - Thomas, Denise L. (Box A-116, Folder 143)
    - Thomas, Dewey (Box A-116, Folder 144)
      Also letter, halftone/promotional card.
    - Thomas, Dick (Box A-116, Folder 145)
    - Thomas, Don M. (Box A-116, Folder 146)
      Photographer if identified: Steve Friedman, News Voice International, George Jervas
    - Thomas, Don Mrs. (Box A-116, Folder 147)
    - Thomas, Donald E. (Box A-116, Folder 148)
      Photographer if identified: Clarence Davis, G. E. Schenectady News
    - Thomas, Douglas L. (Box A-116, Folder 149)
    - Thomas, Duane (Box A-116, Folder 150)
    - Thomas, Eaton (Box A-116, Folder 151)
    - Thomas, Edgar W. (Box A-116, Folder 152)
    - Thomas, Eleanor Mrs. (See Jimmy Adams) (Box A-116, Folder 153)
    - Thomas, Elizabeth (Box A-116, Folder 154)
    - Thomas, Elvira (Box A-116, Folder 155)
    - Thomas, Eugene Mr. (Box A-116, Folder 156)
    - Thomas, Eugene L. F. (Box A-116, Folder 157)
    - Thomas, Evelyn (Box A-116, Folder 158)
    - Thomas, Fayrene (Box A-116, Folder 159)
    - Thomas, Frank (Box A-116, Folder 160)
    - Thomas, Franklin (Box A-116, Folder 161)
    - Thomas, Franklin Mrs. (Box A-116, Folder 162)
    - Thomas, Franklin W. (Box A-116, Folder 163)
      Photographer if identified: Steve Friedman
    - Thomas, Fred (Box A-116, Folder 164)
      Photographer if identified: Bruno of Hollywood, Henry Lawrence, Bill Anderson
    - Thomas, Gary (Box A-116, Folder 165)
      Photographer if identified: Art Photo Studio,
    - Thomas, Rev. George (Box A-116, Folder 166)
      Photographer if identified: King Photographers, Cameron Studios
    - Thomas, George B. Dr. (Box A-116, Folder 167)
    - Thomas, Gerald Eustis (Commander) (Box A-116, Folder 168)
      Photographer if identified: U.S. Navy
    - Thomas, Gertrude (Box A-116, Folder 169)
      Photographer if identified: Whitestone Photo, Chuck Smith
    - Thomas, Gwin (Box A-116, Folder 170)
    - Thomas, Gloria Miss (Box A-116, Folder 171)
      Photographer if identified: James Gilbert, Cecil Layne, Gilbert Pictorial Enterprise, George Jervas, Mallory Photos, Harris Photo, Pictorial Enterprise, Bro. David McAdams
    - Thomas, Harold (Box A-116, Folder 172)
    - Thomas, Harold F. (Box A-116, Folder 173)
    - Thomas, Henry (Box A-116, Folder 174)
    - Thomas, Holly (Box A-116, Folder 175)
    - Thomas, Howard (Box A-116, Folder 176)
    - Thomas, Howard N. (Box A-116, Folder 177)
    - Thomas, Ike (Box A-116, Folder 178)
    - Thomas, Isiah (Box A-116, Folder 179)
    - Thomas, Ivan (Box A-116, Folder 180)
    - Thomas, James (Box A-116, Folder 181)
      Photographer if identified: James Gilbert, C. Ramsey/Dept of Correction
    - Thomas, James (Box A-116, Folder 182)
    - Thomas, James C. (Box A-116, Folder 183)
      Also 1 envelope of negatives, letter.
      Photographer if identified: L. St. Clair Dummett, A. Hansen, Layne's Studio, Smith
    - 1 - Swearing in of James C. Thomas 100 Centre St Dummett (Box A-116, Folder 183)
      Dated 12-19-1952. 1 strip and 3 loose 6"x6" negatives. 5 images total.
    - Thomas, James C. (Box A-116, Folder 184)
      1 envelope of negatives.
    - 1 - James "Cadillac" Thomas Nichols (Box A-116, Folder 184)
      Dated 10-7-1947. 1 4"x5" negative. 1 image total.
    - Thomas, James "Cadillac" (Box A-116, Folder 185)
    - Thomas, James (Pt.) (Box A-116, Folder 186)
      Also 1 envelope of negatives. Two different individuals pictured.
      Photographer if identified: W. Smith, L. St. Clair Dummett
    - 1 - PH James Thomas in hospital (stabbed by motorist) 547 E. 121 St. Bx Smith (Box A-116, Folder 186)
      Dated 3-10-1952. 2 4"x5" negatives. 2 images total.
    - Thomas, James Joshua (Rev.) (Box A-116, Folder 187)
      Photographer if identified: Prince Studios, Photokraft,
    - Thomas, James R. (Box A-116, Folder 188)
    - Thomas, Janice M. (Box A-116, Folder 189)
      Photographer if identified: Van Picture Service
    - Thomas, Jasmine (Box A-116, Folder 190)
    - Thomas, Jean (Box A-116, Folder 191)
      Photographer if identified: Diaz and Lloyd
    - Thomas, Jeanette (Box A-116, Folder 192)
    - Thomas Jefferson H. S. (Box A-116, Folder 193)
    - Thomas, Jeffrey (Box A-116, Folder 194)
      Photographer if identified: Dalman B. I. V.
    - Thomas, Jerome (Box A-116, Folder 195)
    - Jesse O. Thomas (Box A-116, Folder 196)
      Photographer if identified: Johnson/Red Cross, Waller/Red Cross, Daniel Riordan/Red Cross,
    - Thomas, James S. (Box A-116, Folder 197)
    - Thomas, Joe (Wife is Gloria Thomas Schafer Beer) (Box A-116, Folder 198)
    - Thomas, Joe (Box A-116, Folder 199)
      Also 1 envelope of negatives (Dated 4-25-1949; 1 strip of 6"x6" negatives). 2 images total.. One print has staple through edge. 1 print has typescript caption stapled to recto.
      Photographer if identified: Nichols, Harris Photo
    - Thomas, John (Box A-116, Folder 200)
      Also 1 envelope of negatives (Dated 5-29-1951; 1 strip of 6"x6" negatives, 2 images total).
    - Thomas, John (Box A-116, Folder 201)
      Photographer if identified: Cecil Layne, Peterkin Photo, James C. Campbell,
    - Thomas, John (Mr. & Mrs.) (Box A-116, Folder 202)
      Photographer if identified: Roberts Photo Studio
    - Thomas, John B. (Box A-116, Folder 203)
    - Thomas, John D. (Box A-116, Folder 204)
    - Thomas, John Marshall Mr. & Mrs. (Box A-116, Folder 205)
    - Thomas, Johnny (Box A-116, Folder 206)
    - Thomas, Joseph (Box A-116, Folder 207)
    - Thomas, Joseph (Box A-116, Folder 208)
      Print has ms. caption stapled to recto.
    - Thomas, Joseph III (Mr. & Mrs.) (Box A-116, Folder 209)
    - Thomas, Joseph C. (Box A-116, Folder 210)
      Photographer if identified: W. Adrian Brockington
    - Thomas, Mr. & Mrs. Joseph E. (Box A-116, Folder 211)
    - Thomas, Julia (Box A-116, Folder 212)
      Photographer if identified: Bill Hilton
    - Thomas, Julius A. (Box A-116, Folder 213)
      Also one paper stereotype matrix with newspaper clipping of same. One print has staple through edge.
    - Tejador, Charles (Box A-117, Folder 1)
    - Thomas, Franklin A. (Box A-117, Folder 2)
      Also three velox prints. One print has single-leaf typescript adhered on verso with staple on border; one has single-leaf typescript letter attached with paperclip.
      Photographer if identified: Lem Peterkin, Ace Creative Photo, Pope Studio, James Gilbert, Lloyd Yearwood, Dave Greene, James M. Mannas, United Press International Photo, Harris Photo
    - Thomas, K. Carl (Box A-117, Folder 3)
    - Thomas, Karen (Box A-117, Folder 4)
    - Thomas, Kid (Box A-117, Folder 5)
      Folder reads: "Kid Thomas' Preservation Hall Band."
    - Thomas, La Verne (Box A-117, Folder 6)
    - Thomas, Laura (Box A-117, Folder 7)
      Photographer if identified: Morgan Photo Service
    - Thomas, LaVerne (Box A-117, Folder 8)
    - Thomas, Lee (Box A-117, Folder 9)
    - Thomas, Leon (Box A-117, Folder 10)
      Photographer if identified: Studio One, Cecil Layne, Popsie, Pictorial Enterprise
    - Thomas, Lex (Box A-117, Folder 11)
    - Thomas, Lillo (Box A-117, Folder 12)
    - Thomas, Lorenzo J. (Box A-117, Folder 13)
    - Thomas, Lorraine (Box A-117, Folder 14)
    - Thomas, Marie (Box A-117, Folder 15)
      Photographer if identified: Vernon L. Smith, Carl Samrock
    - Thomas, Mary (Mrs.) (Box A-117, Folder 16)
    - Thomas, Marilyn (Box A-117, Folder 17)
    - Thomas, Michael (Box A-117, Folder 18)
      Note on folder: "Miami Vice."
    - Thomas, Miriam (Box A-117, Folder 19)
    - Thomas, Nida E. (Mrs.) (Box A-117, Folder 20)
      Print has typescript leaf press release (three leaves) attached with paperclip.
    - Thomas, Pat (Box A-117, Folder 21)
    - Thomas, Paul M. (Box A-117, Folder 22)
    - Thomas, Philip (Box A-117, Folder 23)
      Also one velox print. One print has single-leaf typescript press release attached with paperclip, one typescript leaf description loose in folder.
      Photographer if identified: Great Exposures, Dave Greene Photo
    - Thomas, Piri (Box A-117, Folder 24)
    - Thomas, Priscilla (Box A-117, Folder 25)
    - Thomas, Richard (Box A-117, Folder 26)
    - Thomas, Robert (Box A-117, Folder 27)
    - Thomas, Robert (Dr.) (Box A-117, Folder 28)
    - Thomas, Roderick D. (Box A-117, Folder 29)
    - Thomas, Rose C. (Dr.) (Box A-117, Folder 30)
    - Thomas, Ron (Box A-117, Folder 31)
    - Thomas, Rudolph J. (Box A-117, Folder 32)
    - Thomas, Rudy (Box A-117, Folder 33)
    - Thomas, Rufus (Box A-117, Folder 34)
    - Thomas, Sam (Box A-117, Folder 35)
    - Thomas, Sandy (Box A-117, Folder 36)